http://www.emergencyuniversity.com/legal/privacy-policy

COVID 19FREE TRAININGMental HealthCOVID-19 Personal ProtectionWORKPLACE SERVICESWORKPLACESEXPERT Q&ATrendingSkills Certification Anywhere, AnytimeFREE Training: Mental HealthFREE Training: COVID-19 Personal ProtectionBusiness Consultations for COVID-19COVID-19 Workplace ProgramsCOVID-19 Questions & AnswersNew Hire EH&S ProgramsSchool ShootersAbout UsWho We AreContact UsBlogPodcastsCareersPressTestimonialsFAQsWhitepapersServicesTechnology SolutionsEmergency Response ProgramsExecutive Protection: MedicalHealth and SafetyTrainingEquipment and SuppliesNew Hire ProgramsStoreOnline TrainingLoginTraineeInstructorAdminIniciar SesiónContact UsPrivacy PolicyEmergency University is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process your payment, establish your account in Maestro™ the Learning Management System, create your login access, provide you with access to the programs you have purchased, track and record your training and testing and confirm completion of your specific courses of instruction, respond to your requests for additional information or resources, and advise you of changes to the Web Site and of Emergency University products or services which may be of interest to you.Please read further about the details of our privacy policy. If you have questions about the privacy of your information provided to Emergency University, please contact our Privacy Officer at privacy@emergencyuniversity.com.Information Collection and Use:When you register with Emergency University, we ask for your name, email address, address, state, zip code, phone number, speed of connection, type of connection, and your Company name when applicable. We allow you to establish your own password. You are not anonymous to us once you register with Emergency University.Emergency University may use this information to tell you about Emergency University products or services which may be of interest to you. Emergency University may use your personal information to contact you either by online electronic communication (such as e-mail), or by regular mail or telephone.Emergency University does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies, except under the following circumstances:Exceptions:You have specifically provided us with consent to share the information;In order to provide you with the products or services you requested.In order to provide you with the products or services you requested we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Emergency University. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.). Emergency University may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Emergency University, our users, or others.Emergency University may collect and disseminate aggregate statistics about the visitors and users of our site and its services, including but not limited to sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.This Privacy Policy covers Emergency University’s treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the Emergency University site, and when you use Emergency University’s services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Emergency University does not own or control, or to people that Emergency University does not employ or manage.Credit Card Transactions: Paymentech and Bank of America process Emergency University’s Credit card transactions. Emergency University chose this professional payment authorization service for added security and reliability. Only the purchase price and the credit card information provided by the customer is supplied to Paymentech and Bank of America. Information collected during transactions is maintained in their database for accounting and billing purposes.Changes to this Privacy PolicyEmergency University may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.Questions or SuggestionsIf you have questions please contact us at privacy@emergencyuniversity.com.PressEU Presents at Citizen CPR FoundationJanuary 1stThe Difference Between Life and DeathJanuary 1stView MoreWho we areAbout UsCareersBlogPodcastsPressTestimonialsFAQContact UsResearchIndustriesCorporationsGovernmentHealthcareHome CareInstructorsIndividualsSchoolsComplianceValidate Certificate2015 AHA CPR GuidelinesState AED RegulationsContact us. Let us customize a solution for your company!Contact UsTerms of Service | Privacy Policy© 2020 Emergency University All Rights Reserved
